Guide to the Civil War Stereographs 1861-1865 PR 65-1
New-York Historical Society
- Brig. Gen. Crawford and staff., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-6)
  Studio portrait of General Crawford and staff.
- Lieut. W.D. Cushing, U.S.N., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-7)
  Studio portrait of Lieut. W.D. Cushing, U.S.N.
- Lt. Washington, a Confederate prisoner, and Capt. Custer, U.S.A., 1862 (Item 779-8)
  J.B. Washington, with George A. Custer, a classmate at West Point, after his capture at Fair Oaks.
- Gen. Custer at his headquarters, ca. 1864, published later (Item 779-9)
  Custer seated outside tent, with dog at his feet.
- Gen. G.A. Custer., 1864, published later (Item 779-10)
  Oval portrait of Custer, looking to his right.
- Gen. G.A. Custer., 1864, published later (Item 779-11)
- Gen. John A. Dix, ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 779-12)
  Portrait of Dix who is famous for his order, "If any man pulls down the American Flag shoot him on the spot."
- Brig. Gen. Abram Duryea [Duryée], Col. 7th Regt. N.Y., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-13)
  Abram Duryée's portrait.
- Col. Duryee and staff at head quarters, Camp Butler, near Fortress Monroe, Va. No. 2., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-14)
  Group portrait of Col. Duryée and staff on the porch of headquarters.
- Vice Admiral David Farragut, U.S.N., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-15)
  Portrait of David Farragut, seated, hat on table.
- Vice Admiral David Farragut, U.S.N., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-16)
  David Farragut's portrait.
- Gen. Ferrero and staff, Petersburg, Va., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-17)
  Group of officers, including Gen. Edward Ferrero, standing on stairs in front of building, columns decorated with bunting.
- Group, Gibson and staff., 1862 (Item 779-18)
  Officers standing around a cannon at Fair Oaks.
- Brig. Gen. Gordon., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-19)
  Portrait of Brig. Gen. Gordon.
- Lieut. Gen'l Ulysses S. Grant, Com. in Chief Armies of U.S., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-20)
  Portrait of Ulysses S. Grant.
- Gen. U.S. Grant, ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-21)
- Lieut. General U.S. Grant hero of a grateful nation., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 779-22)
  Portrait of General Ulysses Grant.
- [Ulysses S. Grant.], ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 779-23)
  U.S. Grant, standing.
- A council of war at Massaponax Church, VA., 21st May, 1864. Gen. Grant leaning over Gen. Meade, examining a map which had just been completed by the topographical engineers. (Item 779-24)
  Group of generals seated on wooden benches relaxing and consulting a map, wagons in the background.
- A council of war at Massaponax Church, VA., 21st May, 1864. Gen. Grant and Meade, Asst. Sec. of War, Dana, and their staff officers. (Item 779-25)
- General Grant's Council of War., 1864, published later (Item 779-26)
- Major Gen. Winfield Scott Hancock., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-27)
  Portrait of Major General Winfield Scott Hancock.
- Gen. Heintzelman and staff, Harrison's Landing, Aug., 1862. (Item 779-28)
  General Heintzelman and staff seated or kneeling on ground.
- Brig. Gen. O.O. Howard., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-29)
  Portrait of General Oliver Otis Howard.
- Gen. Phil. Keanery [Kearny]. Photograph taken in 1863., 1863, published later (Item 779-30)
  Portrait of General Philip Kearny.
- Gen. Phil. Keanery [Kearny]. Photograph taken in 1862., 1862, published later (Item 779-31)
  Portrait of Gen. Phil. Kearny.
- Maj. Gen. Geo. B. McClellan and wife., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-32)
  Portrait of McClellan standing behind his seated wife.
- Group, Gen. Marcy and friends, at Camp Winfield Scott, near Yorktown, May 2, 1862. (Item 779-33)
  General Marcy and others, including civilians, posed for a group portrait.
- Gen'l Marcy and friends at headquarters Army of the Potomac, 4th October, 1862. (Item 779-34)
  General Marcy and others, including civilians, in front of tent at the headquarters of the Army of the Potomac.
- Moseby [Mosby] and his gang of guerillas., ca. 1861-ca. 1865 (Item 779-35)
  Studio portrait of 17 men, including John Mosby.
- Maj. Gen. Ord, wife and child at the mansion formerly occupied by Jeff. Davis, Richmond, Va. In the doorway is the table upon which the surrender of Gen. Lee was signed., 1865 (Item 779-36)
  Family portrait of General Ord and his wife and child.
- Gen'l Pleasonton, September, 1863. (Item 779-37)
  Portrait of General Alfred Pleasonton.
- Gen'l Patrick and staff, near Bealton, Va., September, 1863. (Item 779-38)
  Gen'l Patrick and staff, in front of tent camouflaged with greenery, near Bealton, Va., September, 1863.
- General Patrick (Provost Marshal General Army Potomac) and staff, Culpepper [sic], November, 1863. (Item 779-39)
  General Patrick and staff seated on a porch, Culpeper, Va..
- Group, Major Robertson and friends., 1862 (Item 779-40)
  Group portrait of Major Robertson and other soldiers, each with sword, standing next to cannon.
- Com. John Rogers, U.S.N., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-41)
  Portrait of Commander John Rogers.
- Lieut. Gen. Winfield Scott. U.S.A., [ca. 1861-ca. 1865] (Item 779-42)
  Winfield Scott, seated on porch, holding sword.
- Maj. Gen'l W.T. Sherman, U.S.A., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-43)
  Portrait of General William Tecumseh Sherman.
- Gen. W.T. Sherman, ("Old Tecumseh")., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 779-44)
- Maj. Gen. W. T. Sherman and horse. This view was taken in the trenches before Atlanta, Ga., 1864 (Item 779-45)
  Major General W. T. Sherman and horse near Atlanta, Georgia.
- Maj. Gen. Sherman and staff. This view was taken in the trenches before Atlanta, Ga., 1864 (Item 779-46)
  Major General Sherman and staff standing around a cannon near Atlanta, Georgia.
- Gen. W.T. Sherman and staff. This view was taken in the trenches before Atlanta, Ga., 1864, published later (Item 779-47)
  Major General Sherman and staff standing around a cannon.
- Gen. W.T. Sherman and staff. This view was taken in the trenches before Atlanta, Ga., 1864, published later (Item 779-48)
- Brig. Gen. K. Smith, ca. 1861-ca. 1865 (Item 779-49)
  Bust pose of General Smith, facing left of frame.
- Major-General W.F. Smith, (Baldy Smith) Commander of the 6th Corps. This view was taken near Malvern Hill, during the "seven days' fight" in 1862., 1862, published later (Item 779-50)
  Group portrait of General Smith with other soldiers.
- Col. Strang, Quartermaster., ca. 1861-1865, published later (Item 779-51)
  Col. Strang working at table outside a tent.
- Brig. Gen. Sweeney [Sweeny]., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-52)
  Portrait of General Thomas William Sweeny, face turned to profile.
- Gen. G.H. Thomas, (the Rock of Chickamauga."), ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 779-53)
  Portrait of Gen. G.H. Thomas.
- Lieut. Wheeler from Berkshire, Samuel Williams, attendant., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 779-54)
  Two women and military officers standing outside a tent.
- Com. J.L. Worden., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 779-55)
  Portrait of Commander Worden, who was in command of the "Monitor" when it captured the "Merrimac."
- [Unidentified officers and a civilian in front of a tent], ca. 1861-ca. 1865 (Item 779-56)
  Unidentified officers and a civilian in front of a tent.
- Co. A., 5th Reg. N.Y. Vol., 1861, ca.1861 (Item 780-1)
  Zouaves lined up in formation.
- Col. Duryea's [Duryée] Zouaves, ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 780-2)
  Col. Duryée's Zouaves lined up in formation at Fort Monroe.
- [Group of soldiers and officers in unidentified camp] (Item 780-3)
  Group of soldiers and officers in unidentified camp, tents in background.
- The hero of Gettysburg., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 780-4)
  War veteran John Burns seated outside in a rocking chair with his musket propped near the door to a building.
- Hard Tack, ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 780-5)
  Soldier seated on a wooden crate full of hard tack.
- A cavalry orderly., 1862, published later (Item 780-6)
  An orderly standing next to a horse.
- Our boys in the trenches., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 780-7)
  Soldiers seated on the edge of trench which is covered with make-shift tents.
- The sally-port and draw-bridge., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 780-8)
  Soldiers standing on a draw-bridge in front of cannon.
- Group at Mr. Foller's farm, Cumberland., 1862 (Item 780-9)
  Group of soldiers, African-American men, and African-American boys seated on logs out in the woods.
- [Soldiers in formation with a drummer in the rear left corner.], ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 780-10)
  Soldiers in formation with a drummer in the rear left corner.
- Lamar Rifles, taken on Main St. at side of Court House Square., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 780-11)
  Soldiers lined up at the town square with rifles.
- View looking South, showing how the Rebels destroyed the Orange and Alexandria Railroad when they fell back before the Army of the Potomac, under General Meade, October 13, 1863. (Item 781-1)
  Ripped up railroad ties and twisted metal with men standing in the background.
- [Soldiers guarding railroad equipment.], ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 781-2)
  Soldiers guarding railroad equipment.
- The famous relay house on the B.O.R.R, ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 781-3)
  Soldiers sitting on platform near relay house on the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad.
- Destruction of a railroad bridge., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 781-4)
  Rubble of a destroyed railroad bridge.
- Fort Morgan. View of Citadel, looking south-west, showing the effect of Farragut's terrific bombardment., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 782-1)
  Looking southwest at Fort Morgan, showing collapsed roof, and rubble-strewn yard.
- General McClellan's Headquarters, Washington, D.C., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 783-1)
  McClellan's Headquarters building.
- Capt. John's Run, near Washington., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 783-2)
  Boat on shore of Potomac with a man on deck.
- Georgetown ferry., 1862 (Item 783-3)
  Men standing on the rocks at the shore with the wagons on the Georgetown ferry and a bridge in the background.
- Sherman's Grand Army. Looking up Pennsylvania Ave. from the Treasury Building, Maj. Gen. Logan and staff and Army of Tennessee passing in review., 1865 (Item 783-4)
  People lining the street at corner, as Maj. Gen. John A. Logan and Army of Tennessee pass in review.
- G. The Army of the Potomac. Looking up Pennsylvania Avenue from the Treasury Buildings. Maj. Gen. Humphrey and staff on horseback, and 2d Army Corps in ranks beyond., 1865 (Item 783-5)
  Officers, including Major General Andrew Humphrey, on horseback on Pennsylvania Avenue, soldiers in ranks in background.
- The Army of the Potomac. Looking up Pennsylvania Avenue from the Treasury Building, troops of Maj. Gen. Parks and 9th Army Corps passing in review., 1865 (Item 783-6)
  Lead horses beginning to make a turn, troops of the 9th Army Corps arrayed behind.
- Sherman's Grand Army. Looking up Pennsylvania Ave. from the Treasury Buildings, Maj. Gen. Logan and staff and Army of Tennessee passing in review., 1865 (Item 783-7)
  Crowds in the foreground, and lining the street, as officers on horses, including General John Logan, lead the Army of Tennessee on parade.
- Sherman's Grand Army. Looking up Pennsylvania Avenue from the Treasury Buildings, during the passage of the 20th Army Corps., 1865 (Item 783-8)
  Wide avenue, with soldiers led by officers on horses on the right side of the street.
- Grand review of the Army of the Potomac looking up Pennsylvania Avenue from the Treasury Building. Major-General Wright and the 6th Army Corps passing in review., 1865, published later (Item 783-9)
  Large group of soldiers making the corner in formation, nearly filling the street.
- The Army of the Potomac looking up Pennsylvania Avenue from Treasury Building a Division of Artillery pass in review., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 783-10)
  Division of Artillery from the Army of the Potomac passing in review, officers on horseback, followed by caissons.
- [Grand review of returning soldiers at Washington, May 23rd and 24th, 1865. Gen. Grant, Fred Grant, Sec. Stanton, Pres. Johnson.] (Item 783-11)
  The reviewing stand with guests at the Grand Review of returning soldiers at Washington, May 23rd and 24th, with honor guard of soldiers in front.
- Grand review of returning soldiers at Washington, May 23rd and 24th, 1865. Gen. Grant, Fred Grant, Sec. Stanton, Pres. Johnson. (Item 783-12)
  The reviewing stand with guest at the Grand Review of returning soldiers at Washington, May 23rd and 24th, with honor guard of soldiers in front.
- Signal tower, Jacksonville, Fla., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 784-1)
  Signal tower with houses in the background.
- Signal tower, Jacksonville, Fla., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 784-2)
- Old Spanish fortress of St. Augustine., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 784-3)
  Interior of old Spanish fortress of St. Augustine, soldiers, cannons and cannonballs.
- Fort Marion, St. Augustine, Florida., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 784-4)
  Walls and battlements Fort Marion, St. Augustine, Florida.
- Fort Pulaski ?, April 10-11, 1862, ca.1862 (Item 785-1)
  Fort believed to be Fort Pulaski (Ga.) showing earthworks and walls.
- Fort Pulaski ?, April 10-11, 1862, ca.1862 (Item 785-2)
  Fort believed to be Fort Pulaski (Ga.), from road, showing walls of the fort.
- Interior of Fort Pulaski after the bombardment., ca. 1862 (Item 785-3)
  Interior of Fort Pulaski (Ga.) after the bombardment, showing brick arches and rubble.
- Fort Pulaski after bombardment, Apr. 10-11, 1862 (Item 785-4)
  Fort Pulaski after bombardment, showing damage to the outer walls.
- Fort McAllister, taken Dec. 13th 1864 after a 15 minute fite [sic]. Sherman's last obstacle (Item 785-5)
  Trenches with chevaux-de-frise, outside Fort McAllister.
- General Sherman's men dismounting Rebel guns from Fort McAllister., 1864 (Item 785-6)
  General Sherman's men dismounting cannons from Fort McAllister using block and tackle hanging from tripod.
- Interior of the Rebel Fort McAllister, Savannah, Ga., looking east, showing the place where Sherman's men carried the place by storm., 1864 (Item 785-7)
  Interior of the Fort McAllister, Savannah, Ga., looking east, showing earthworks and abatis.
- Fort McAllister, ca. 1864 (Item 785-8)
  Fort McAllister, Georgia, showing earthworks and abatis.
- Dismounted mortar, Fort Pulaski, GA, 1862 (Item 785-9)
  Dismounted mortar and debris at Fort Pulaski, Ga.
- Whitehall Street, Atlanta, Ga., 1863 (Item 786-1)
  Whitehall Street with line of covered wagons passing down the street.
- Front House and Masonic Hall, Marietta St., Atlanta., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 786-2)
  Marietta Street with large buildings in the background with smaller dwellings in the foreground.
- Railroad depot, round house and machine shops, Atlanta, Ga., 1863 (Item 786-3)
  Railroad depot, round house and machine shops, Atlanta, Ga. with a group of men standing in train yard, tracks in the foreground.
- Mich. Engineers destroying rails and engine boiler and machinery near the depot, ruins of machine shop, 1865 (Item 786-4)
  Soldiers of the 1st Michigan Engineers looking on as rails, engine boiler and machinery is destroyed near the depot, ruins of machine shop in the background.
- Depot, north side, view looking north west, round house and machine shops of Atlanta & Western R.R., ca. 1864 (Item 786-5)
  Depot and tracks, with machine shops in the background.
- Where Gen. McPherson was killed., 1864 (Item 786-6)
  Wagon wheels against trees and a sign nailed to a tree marking the spot where McPherson was killed.
- The place where Maj. Gen. J. B. McPherson was killed, Atlanta, Ga., 1864 (Item 786-7)
- Rebel fort on the Marrietta Road, north of the City, Atlanta, Ga., ca.1864 (Item 786-8)
  Rebel fort with what is probably the photographer's wagon and dark tent in middle ground beyond the chevaux-de-frise.
- Gen. Sherman's men tearing up the railroad before leaving Atlanta, Ga., ca.1864 (Item 786-9)
  Gen. Sherman's men using lever to pull up rails before leaving Atlanta.
- Gen. Sherman's soldiers tearing up the railroad, before leaving Atlanta, Ga., ca.1864 (Item 786-10)
- The place where Maj. Gen. J. B. McPherson was killed, Atlanta, Ga., 1864 (Item 786-11)
  Wagon wheels against trees and a sign in the distance nailed to a tree marking the spot where McPherson was killed.
- The place where Maj. Gen. J. B. McPherson was killed, Atlanta, Ga., 1864 (Item 786-12)
- Rebel fortifications, Atlanta, Ga., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 786-13)
  Fortification with soldiers and cannons.
- How Sherman's boys fixed the railroad., ca.1864, published later (Item 786-14)
  Soldier piling up ties and rails for burning.
- Sherman's men destroying railroad., 1864, published later (Item 786-15)
  1st Michigan Engineers destroying rails and engine boiler and machinery near the depot, ruins of machine shop in the background.
- Preparing for the "March to the Sea.", ca.1864, published later (Item 786-16)
  Train cars and covered wagons loaded with gear and people, the last cars to leave Atlanta before Union troops destroyed the railroad.
- On the lines near Atlanta., 1864, published later (Item 786-17)
  Potter House damaged by Union artillery.
- Picket Station near Atlanta, Ga., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 786-18)
  Picket post with soldiers relaxing among trees near building just visible at right.
- Picket Station near Atlanta, Ga., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 786-19)
  Picket post with soldiers relaxing outside in front of building.
- Group of Union troop defending the viaduct on the Baltimore and Ohio Rail Road., after 1863 (Item 787-1)
  Group portrait of men and a boy seated and standing on hill overlooking the viaduct over the Patapsco River.
- Ruins of P. M. Gen'l M. Blair's residence, MD. Destroyed by the rebel raiders July 12, 1864. (Item 787-2)
  Frame of destroyed house with people in the foreground surveying the damage.
- Crew of the Army gun boat Foster, practising [sic] with howitzer guns, Point of Rocks., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 787-3)
  Sailors in a field with artillery.
- Principal street in Sharpsburg, Maryland., 1862 (Item 787-4)
  Dirt road dividing rows of houses.
- Lutheran church, Sharpsburg, Maryland., 1862 (Item 787-5)
  Church with fences out front and damage done to the side.
- Street in Sharpsburg. Episcopal church in the distance., 1862 (Item 787-6)
  Street in Sharpsburg, wagon, home and fence in foreground, Episcopal church in the distance.
- Pontoon bridge across the Potomac at Berlin., ca. 1863 (Item 787-7)
  The Potomac River with soldier on horseback near the bridge.
- Ruins of bridge across the Potomac, at Berlin, destroyed by the Confederates, June 1861. (Item 787-8)
  Houses near the Potomac river, piers of destroyed bridge standing in the river.
- A contrast. Federal buried; Confederate unburied, where they fell on the battle field of Antietam., 1863 (Item 788-1)
  Man standing over grave of Union soldier and body of Confederate soldier on a battlefield.
- A contrast. Federal buried; Confederate unburied, where they fell on the battle field of Antietam., 1863 (Item 788-2)
- Ditch on the right wing, where Kimbal[l]'s brigade fought so desperately at the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-3)
  Ditch filled with war dead.
- "The sunken road" at Antietam. A Union battery succeeded in getting an excellent range of this road and slaughtered the enemy like sheep., 1862 (Item 788-4)
- He sleeps his last sleep. A Confederate soldier who after being wounded had evidently dragged himself to a little ravine on the hill side, where he died., 1862 (Item 788-5)
  A Confederate soldier who after being wounded had evidently dragged himself to a little ravine on the hill side, where he lies in a depression in the grassy field.
- Confederate soldiers as they fell, near the Burnside Bridge, at the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-6)
  Two dead soldiers on the battlefield at Antietam.
- Confederate soldiers as they fell, near the Burnside Bridge, at the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-7)
- Gathered together for burial after the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-8)
  Dead soldiers lined up on the ground awaiting burial.
- Dead. Horse of Confederate Colonel both killed at the Battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-9)
  Dead horse in a field.
- Horse of Confederate colonel both killed at the Battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-10)
- Killed at the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-11)
  Dead soldiers near a wooden fence.
- Burying the dead after the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-12)
  Soldiers digging graves for the dead soldiers.
- View in ditch on the right wing after the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-13)
  Ditch filled with dead soldiers and debris.
- View in ditch on the right wing after the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-14)
- View in ditch on the right wing after the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-15)
- View of ditch on right wing, which had been used as a rifle pit by the Confederates at the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-16)
  Soldiers looking at dead soldiers in a ditch.
- Confederate soldiers as they fell at the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-17)
  Three dead soldiers in front of wooden fence.
- View on battle field. Group of Louisiana regiment as they fell at the battle of Antietam. The contest at this point had been very severe., 1862 (Item 788-18)
- View on battle field of Antietam where Sumner's corps charged the enemy. Scene of terrific conflict., 1862 (Item 788-19)
  View on battle field of Antietam where Sumner's corps charged the enemy: dead soldiers litter the battle field.
- View on battle field of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-20)
  Soldiers seated near tree with dead soldiers around them.
- A lone grave on battle field of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-21)
  Lone grave next to a tree with soldiers around it, two with guns on shoulders, apparently keeping guard.
- A lone grave on battle field of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-22)
- View on battle field of Antietam near Sherrick's house, where the 79th New York Volunteers fought after they crossed the creek. Group of dead Confederates., 1862 (Item 788-23)
  Two dead Confederate soldiers lying in a field.
- Dunker church, on battle field of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-24)
  Church building with wooden fence in front.
- Ruins of Mumma's house, on battle field of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-25)
  Ruins of Mumma's house, on battle field of Antietam with other buildings in the background, Gardner's wagon dark room at extreme left.
- Gen'l Hooker's headquarters during the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-26)
  A large brick house, the home of Philip Pry, General McClellan's headquarters during the battle of Antietam.
- Group, Gen'l Caldwell and staff on battle field of Antietam, 21st September, 1862. (Item 788-27)
  Group portrait of General Caldwell and staff in front of a tent with the American flag draped over the front.
- Pic-nic party at Antietam bridge, 22d September, 1862. (Item 788-28)
  Horse drawn carriage near the Antietam bridge, two women and two men also pictured.
- Antietam bridge on Sharpsburgh and Boonsboro' turnpike., 1862 (Item 788-29)
  Antietam bridge with buildings in the background.
- Burnside bridge, Antietam, looking up stream., 1862 (Item 788-30)
  Burnside bridge, Antietam, looking up stream with wooden barrels in the water.
- Smith's barn, near Keedysville, used as a hospital after the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-31)
  Smith's barn, near Keedysville, used as a hospital after the battle of Antietam.
- Smith's house and barn, near Keedysville, used as a hospital after the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-32)
  Smith's house and barn, near Keedysville, used as a hospital after the battle of Antietam.
- Smith's house and barn, near Keedysville, used as a hospital after the battle of Antietam., 1862 (Item 788-33)
  Tents and huts near Smith's house and barn, near Keedysville, used as a hospital after the battle of Antietam.